A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Peter Mirto, Malcolm Wilson, 1970 January 20; 1008.15/2921 - 1008.15/2923 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Clinton Dominick, Eugene Levy, 1970 January 27; 1008.15/2924 (Box 9)
  - Hyatt House, Republican Women, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 February 2; 1008.15/2925 - 1008.15/2932 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Miss Indian USA, Boy Scouts, 1970 February 9; 1008.15/2960 - 1008.15/2973 (Box 9)
  - Joseph P. King. Donald J. Wickman, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 February 9; 1008.15/2974 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Public Service Commissioner Joseph Swidler, 1970 February 10; 1008.15/2933 - 1008.15/2937 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Press Conference, 1970 February 11; 1008.15/2938 - 1008.15/2939 (Box 9)
    - Red Room. Massachusettes Transit Bill Signing, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Pisani, Assemblyman VanCott, Senator Brydges, Assemblyman Duryea, William Burns, John McCarthy, Gene Parker, Senator Giaffie, Senator Gordon, Senator Lent, Senator Flynn, Senator Barrons, Bun Smith, Assemblyman Jerabek, Senator Burrows, Ralph Marino, Assemblyman Ballatta, Assemblyman Margiatta, Milton Jonas, William Stephens, Senator Calmmerer, Vito Battisti, Joe Kunzeman. Mr. Acker, 1970 February 23; 1008.15/2940 - 1008.15/2952
  - Red Room. Business and Professional Women, 1970 February 23; 1008.15/2953 - 1008.15/2956 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Queens Group, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Ginsbery, 1970 February 23; 1008.15/2957 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Red Cross Group, 1970 February 23; 1008.15/2958 - 1008.15/2959 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receives poppy from American Legion Auxiliary, Poughkeepsie chapter, 1970 February 23; 1008.15/2962 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Press Conference, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblymen Field, Skuse, Pearce, Hall, Senators Brydges, Goodman, Conklin, Skim, Speaker Duryea, 1970 February 24; 1008.15/2975 -1008.15/2976 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, John Scott, author of Book of Prayers, 1970 February 24; 1008.15/2977 - 1008.15/2978 (Box 9)
  - Contacts of Barry Van Lare, 1970 March 2; 1008.15/2979 - 1008.15/2983 (Box 9)
  - Earl Brydges. Lockport High School Honor Society, 1970 March 2; 1008.15/2984 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jack Kemp, Senator Brydges, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/2985 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Consumer Protection Bill, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Greenberg, John Dunne, John Hurt Ferry, Alvin Surhin, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/2986 - 1008.15/2987 (Box 9)
  - League of Women Voters, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/2988 - 1008.15/3010 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller receives tickets to Rochester Lancers soccer team, Charles Schiano, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/3011 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. 4H clubs with Alton Marshall, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/3012 - 1008.15/3023 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. "People and Progress" theme unveiled for 1970 Empire State Fair, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mr. Potter, Dr. Wickham, 1970 March 3; 1008.15/3024 - 1008.15/3026 (Box 9)
  - Vassar College. Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks, 1970 March 4; 1008.15/3027 - 1008.15/3036 (Box 9)
  - Convicts' art. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Brydges, John Casscles, 1970 March 9; 1008.15/3037 - 1008.15/3039 (Box 9)
  - Capitol, Mr. Douglas, Assemblyman Ginsberg, 1970 March 9; 1008.15/3040 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Shuemaker, Senator LaVerne, Teenage Republicans, 1970 March 10; 1008.15/3041 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. James Cameron accepts plaque from the Little People for Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Eugene Partridge, 1970 March 10; 1008.15/3042 (Box 9)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Passanentige, Michael Kashn and mother, 1970 March 10; 1008.15/3043 - 1008.15/3044 (Box 9)
  - SUNY Plattsburg, Building dedication, 1970 March 18; 1008.15/3045 - 1008.15/3053 (Box 9)
  - Hotel Syracuse, 118th New York Press Association Convention, 1970 March 18; 1008.15/3054 - 1008.15/3056 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Speaker Perry Duryea, 1970 March 18; 1008.15/3057 - 1008.15/3068 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. New York State Farm Bureau, 1970 March 18; 1008.15/3069 - 1008.15/3071 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3072 - 1008.15/3082 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. "Boy of the Year" Award, James Heath, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3083 - 1008.15/3086 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Captain Robert Connor sworn in as Commander of NYS. Naval Malitia, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3087 - 1008.15/3088 (Box 9)
  - DeWitt Clinton Hotel, Teenage Republican Meeting, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3089 - 1008.15/3093 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Mansion, Girl Scouts, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3094 - 1008.15/3104 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. CBS "A Day with the Governor," Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 March 23; 1008.15/3105 - 1008.15/3118 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Ginsburg, 1970 April 13; 1008.15/3119- 1008.15/3122 (Box 9)
  - Mayor Alvin Ruskin and family, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 April 14; 1008.15/3123 - 1008.15/3124 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. West Point Cadets, 1970 April 14; 1008.15/3125 - 1008.15/3128 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Mansion, Mayor Lindsay, 1970 April 15; 1008.15/3129 - 1008.15/3130 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Pen Central Modernization Group, 1970 April 16; 1008.15/3131 (Box 9)
  - Assemblyman Duryea, Speaker, Senator Brydges, Watching Apollo 13, 1970 April 17; 1008.15/3132 - 1008.15/3133 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, group, 1970 April 19; 1008.15/3134 - 1008.15/3135 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Ross Bicycle, 1970 April 22; 1008.15/3136 - 1008.15/3139 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Environmental Protection Act, 1970 April 22; 1008.15/3140 - 1008.15/3149 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Teachers Retirement Bill, 1970 April 22; 1008.15/3150 - 1008.15/3154 (Box 9)
  - Hyatt House, Religious Convocation on Drug Abuse, Rev. Koerber, Rabbi Morris Kertzer, Rev. Robert Cobb, Rev. Theodore Conklin, Rabbi Kloperman, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Lefkowitz, Milton Luger, Archbishop Terence Cardinal Cooke, Rev. Emerson Moore, Bishop Ralph Ward, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3155 - 1008.15/3162 (Box 9)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller friend, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3163 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Mr. Levine (CSEA), 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3164 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Miscellaneous Bills, Rabbi Gilbert Klaperman, Rev. Robert Cobb, Bishop Ralph Ward. Rev. Emerson Moore, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3165 - 1008.15/3172 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. group, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3173 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. CSEA Bill, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3174 - 1008.15/3186 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Mrs. DeLong, grandchildren, 1970 May 5; 1008.15/3187 - 1008.15/3188 (Box 9)
  - Hyatt House. NYS. Committee on Mental Health, 1970 May 26; 1008.15/3189 - 1008.15/3203 (Box 9)
  - Guilderland. NY Power Pool Dedication Ceremony, John Vogel, Paul Shore, Edward Nelson, Rev. DeForest, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Wells Allen, Jr., R.A. Merrill, Jr., W. Balet, G.W. Duda, J.L. McCoy, Jr., E. O'Connor, J. Swidler, W.L. Ketcham, George Laird, Maj. Galvin, James O'Neill, Alton Marshall, 1970 May 26; 1008.15/3192 - 1008.15/3201 (Box 9)
  - NYS. Police Acadamy Dedications, 1970 May 26; 1008.15/3204 - 1008.15/3215 (Box 9)
  - Albany's Mayor's Office, Urban Development Corp., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mayor Corning, Joe Madonna, H.J. Lesko, 1970 June 22; 1008.15/3216 - 1008.15/3222 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Awarding Grants to the Fine Arts, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Seymour Knox, Agnes DeMille, Ed Smits, Senator Brydges, Edward Lawrence, William Vick, John Blum, Frederick Stock, Lewis Swyer, Ewald Nyquist, Claudia McNeil, Mrs. David Levene, Lawrence Abrams, Jean Dalrymple, Theodore Nancock, Theodore Hollenbach, 1970 September 10; 1008.15/3223 - 1008.15/3240 (Box 9)
  - Hyatt House, NYS. Press Association Luncheon, 1970 September 28; 1008.15/3241 - 1008.15/3253 (Box 9)
  - Demolition of Ten Eyck Hotel, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mayor Corning, Edward Logue, 1970 October 2; 1008.15/3254 - 1008.15/3272 (Box 9)
  - Assembly Chamber, Press Conference, 1970 November 10; 1008.15/3273 - 1008.15/3279 (Box 9)
  - New Dunn Memorial Bridge Opening, 1970 December 21; 1008.15/3280 - 1008.15/3286 (Box 9)
  - untitled (Box 9)